{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549820728752","data":{"timestamp":" 1549820728752"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 71677cb9-040f-43ae-9588-147f323996ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kitabu"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ki"," userResponse":" ki"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549820729356","data":{"timestamp":" 1549820729356"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 71677cb9-040f-43ae-9588-147f323996ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kitabu"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ta"," userResponse":" ta"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549820730194","data":{"timestamp":" 1549820730194"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 71677cb9-040f-43ae-9588-147f323996ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kitabu"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" bu"," userResponse":" bu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549820734273","data":{"timestamp":" 1549820734273"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 71677cb9-040f-43ae-9588-147f323996ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_angani"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549820735040","data":{"timestamp":" 1549820735040"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 71677cb9-040f-43ae-9588-147f323996ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_angani"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nga"," userResponse":" nga"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549820735698","data":{"timestamp":" 1549820735698"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 71677cb9-040f-43ae-9588-147f323996ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_angani"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ni"," userResponse":" ni"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549820740333","data":{"timestamp":" 1549820740333"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 71677cb9-040f-43ae-9588-147f323996ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mguu"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549820740767","data":{"timestamp":" 1549820740767"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 71677cb9-040f-43ae-9588-147f323996ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mguu"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" gu"," userResponse":" gu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549820741143","data":{"timestamp":" 1549820741143"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 71677cb9-040f-43ae-9588-147f323996ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mguu"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549820745784","data":{"timestamp":" 1549820745784"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 71677cb9-040f-43ae-9588-147f323996ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_sungura"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" su"," userResponse":" su"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549820746203","data":{"timestamp":" 1549820746203"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 71677cb9-040f-43ae-9588-147f323996ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_sungura"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ngu"," userResponse":" ngu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549820746562","data":{"timestamp":" 1549820746562"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 71677cb9-040f-43ae-9588-147f323996ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_sungura"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ra"," userResponse":" ra"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549820750299","data":{"timestamp":" 1549820750299"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 71677cb9-040f-43ae-9588-147f323996ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kwaheri"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kwa"," userResponse":" kwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549820750682","data":{"timestamp":" 1549820750682"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 71677cb9-040f-43ae-9588-147f323996ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kwaheri"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" he"," userResponse":" he"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549820751058","data":{"timestamp":" 1549820751058"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 71677cb9-040f-43ae-9588-147f323996ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kwaheri"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ri"," userResponse":" ri"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549820754992","data":{"timestamp":" 1549820754992"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 71677cb9-040f-43ae-9588-147f323996ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_chakula"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" cha"," userResponse":" cha"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549820755383","data":{"timestamp":" 1549820755383"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 71677cb9-040f-43ae-9588-147f323996ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_chakula"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ku"," userResponse":" ku"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549820755733","data":{"timestamp":" 1549820755733"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 71677cb9-040f-43ae-9588-147f323996ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_chakula"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" la"," userResponse":" la"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549820760393","data":{"timestamp":" 1549820760393"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 71677cb9-040f-43ae-9588-147f323996ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_hasira"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ha"," userResponse":" ha"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549820761178","data":{"timestamp":" 1549820761178"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 71677cb9-040f-43ae-9588-147f323996ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_hasira"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" si"," userResponse":" si"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549820762496","data":{"timestamp":" 1549820762496"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 71677cb9-040f-43ae-9588-147f323996ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_hasira"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ra"," userResponse":" ra"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549820767404","data":{"timestamp":" 1549820767403"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 71677cb9-040f-43ae-9588-147f323996ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mlima"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549820768376","data":{"timestamp":" 1549820768375"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 71677cb9-040f-43ae-9588-147f323996ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mlima"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549820769290","data":{"timestamp":" 1549820769290"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 71677cb9-040f-43ae-9588-147f323996ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mlima"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ma"," userResponse":" ma"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549820772729","data":{"timestamp":" 1549820772729"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 71677cb9-040f-43ae-9588-147f323996ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_zawadi"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" za"," userResponse":" za"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549820773137","data":{"timestamp":" 1549820773137"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 71677cb9-040f-43ae-9588-147f323996ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_zawadi"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wa"," userResponse":" wa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549820773444","data":{"timestamp":" 1549820773444"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 71677cb9-040f-43ae-9588-147f323996ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_zawadi"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" di"," userResponse":" di"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549820777345","data":{"timestamp":" 1549820777345"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 71677cb9-040f-43ae-9588-147f323996ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mjomba"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549820777633","data":{"timestamp":" 1549820777633"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 71677cb9-040f-43ae-9588-147f323996ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mjomba"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" jo"," userResponse":" jo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549820777864","data":{"timestamp":" 1549820777864"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 71677cb9-040f-43ae-9588-147f323996ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mjomba"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mba"," userResponse":" mba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549820780384","data":{"timestamp":" 1549820780383"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 71677cb9-040f-43ae-9588-147f323996ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_mjomba"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..10.off1.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549820792070","data":{"timestamp":" 1549820792069"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 71677cb9-040f-43ae-9588-147f323996ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_mjomba"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549820809754","data":{"timestamp":" 1549820809754"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 90ea26aa-ff14-4aff-b262-1e0b9c532b14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulienda katika sherehe ya Dasara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SOTE"," userResponse":" SOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549820810406","data":{"timestamp":" 1549820810406"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 90ea26aa-ff14-4aff-b262-1e0b9c532b14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulienda katika sherehe ya Dasara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" TULIENDA"," userResponse":" DASARA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549820812567","data":{"timestamp":" 1549820812567"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 90ea26aa-ff14-4aff-b262-1e0b9c532b14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulienda katika sherehe ya Dasara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" TULIENDA"," userResponse":" SHEREHE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549820814338","data":{"timestamp":" 1549820814338"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 90ea26aa-ff14-4aff-b262-1e0b9c532b14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulienda katika sherehe ya Dasara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIENDA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549820814363","data":{"timestamp":" 1549820814363"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 90ea26aa-ff14-4aff-b262-1e0b9c532b14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Sote tulienda katika sherehe ya Dasara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549820814503","data":{"timestamp":" 1549820814503"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 90ea26aa-ff14-4aff-b262-1e0b9c532b14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulienda katika sherehe ya Dasara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIENDA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549820822706","data":{"timestamp":" 1549820822706"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 90ea26aa-ff14-4aff-b262-1e0b9c532b14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Sote tulienda katika sherehe ya Dasara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549820840997","data":{"timestamp":" 1549820840997"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 5671fe33-9837-4a34-af5a-ee0972f3d537"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_c_a"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549820864736","data":{"timestamp":" 1549820864736"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 5671fe33-9837-4a34-af5a-ee0972f3d537"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__tini"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549820873601","data":{"timestamp":" 1549820873601"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 5671fe33-9837-4a34-af5a-ee0972f3d537"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__ita"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549820882310","data":{"timestamp":" 1549820882310"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 5671fe33-9837-4a34-af5a-ee0972f3d537"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__mba"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549820891797","data":{"timestamp":" 1549820891797"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 5671fe33-9837-4a34-af5a-ee0972f3d537"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__kila"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549820900994","data":{"timestamp":" 1549820900994"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 5671fe33-9837-4a34-af5a-ee0972f3d537"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__iye"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549820909310","data":{"timestamp":" 1549820909309"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 5671fe33-9837-4a34-af5a-ee0972f3d537"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__iye"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549820922514","data":{"timestamp":" 1549820922514"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 5671fe33-9837-4a34-af5a-ee0972f3d537"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__wovu"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549820932285","data":{"timestamp":" 1549820932284"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 5671fe33-9837-4a34-af5a-ee0972f3d537"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__wovu"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549820944116","data":{"timestamp":" 1549820944116"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 5671fe33-9837-4a34-af5a-ee0972f3d537"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__wovu"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549820952081","data":{"timestamp":" 1549820952081"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 5671fe33-9837-4a34-af5a-ee0972f3d537"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__imbi"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549820961830","data":{"timestamp":" 1549820961830"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 5671fe33-9837-4a34-af5a-ee0972f3d537"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__apya"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549820970464","data":{"timestamp":" 1549820970464"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 5671fe33-9837-4a34-af5a-ee0972f3d537"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__apya"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549820980763","data":{"timestamp":" 1549820980763"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 5671fe33-9837-4a34-af5a-ee0972f3d537"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__ungu"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549820987803","data":{"timestamp":" 1549820987803"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 5671fe33-9837-4a34-af5a-ee0972f3d537"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__ungu"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549820995779","data":{"timestamp":" 1549820995779"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 5671fe33-9837-4a34-af5a-ee0972f3d537"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__ungu"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821003744","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821003743"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 5671fe33-9837-4a34-af5a-ee0972f3d537"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__ungu"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821013477","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821013477"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 5671fe33-9837-4a34-af5a-ee0972f3d537"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__enu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821022595","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821022594"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 5671fe33-9837-4a34-af5a-ee0972f3d537"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write__enu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821029181","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821029181"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" a2ee359e-1c4e-4d60-bfd5-f1ce9f6d0249"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" START"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821046341","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821046340"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" a2ee359e-1c4e-4d60-bfd5-f1ce9f6d0249"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" END"," userResponse":" END"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821048963","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821048963"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" a2ee359e-1c4e-4d60-bfd5-f1ce9f6d0249"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821049069","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821049069"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" a2ee359e-1c4e-4d60-bfd5-f1ce9f6d0249"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ENDPROBLEM"," userResponse":" ENDPROBLEM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" ENDPROBLEM"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.6.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821060369","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821060369"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 70c1fd3f-ab51-4e4b-9455-66166a5b6567"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.6.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_vidole_vidole-aliita-mrushe"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" vidole"," userResponse":" vidole"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.6.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821065721","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821065721"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 70c1fd3f-ab51-4e4b-9455-66166a5b6567"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.6.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nipate_kimori-angani-nipate"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nipate"," userResponse":" nipate"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.6.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821070938","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821070938"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 70c1fd3f-ab51-4e4b-9455-66166a5b6567"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.6.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_matata_kivuli-kupata-matata"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" matata"," userResponse":" matata"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.6.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821076541","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821076541"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 70c1fd3f-ab51-4e4b-9455-66166a5b6567"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.6.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_lazima_ambalo-dadake-lazima"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" lazima"," userResponse":" lazima"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.6.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821082014","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821082014"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 70c1fd3f-ab51-4e4b-9455-66166a5b6567"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.6.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_hawezi_kuacha-hawezi-uwanja"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" hawezi"," userResponse":" hawezi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.6.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821087986","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821087985"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 70c1fd3f-ab51-4e4b-9455-66166a5b6567"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.6.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_alitia_alitia-kupika-chindi"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" alitia"," userResponse":" kupika"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.6.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821093974","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821093974"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 70c1fd3f-ab51-4e4b-9455-66166a5b6567"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.6.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_alitia_alitia-kupika-chindi"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" alitia"," userResponse":" alitia"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.6.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821099302","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821099302"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 70c1fd3f-ab51-4e4b-9455-66166a5b6567"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.6.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mashua_mzinga-mashua-mpunzi"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mashua"," userResponse":" mashua"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.6.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821104443","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821104443"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 70c1fd3f-ab51-4e4b-9455-66166a5b6567"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.6.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mweupe_mweupe-milima-khalai"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mweupe"," userResponse":" mweupe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.6.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821109497","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821109497"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 70c1fd3f-ab51-4e4b-9455-66166a5b6567"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.6.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kupiga_jasusi-kupiga-rahisi"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kupiga"," userResponse":" kupiga"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.6.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821114672","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821114671"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 70c1fd3f-ab51-4e4b-9455-66166a5b6567"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.6.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mtende_vijana-wazazi-mtende"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mtende"," userResponse":" mtende"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.6.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821120417","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821120417"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 70c1fd3f-ab51-4e4b-9455-66166a5b6567"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.6.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_mtende_vijana-wazazi-mtende"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821133365","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821133365"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 0ebd78dc-f598-4308-9684-e5c5adca2810"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821133595","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821133594"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 0ebd78dc-f598-4308-9684-e5c5adca2810"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821134559","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821134559"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 0ebd78dc-f598-4308-9684-e5c5adca2810"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821135842","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821135841"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 0ebd78dc-f598-4308-9684-e5c5adca2810"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821138782","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821138782"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 0ebd78dc-f598-4308-9684-e5c5adca2810"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821139624","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821139624"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 0ebd78dc-f598-4308-9684-e5c5adca2810"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821139937","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821139937"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 0ebd78dc-f598-4308-9684-e5c5adca2810"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821141170","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821141170"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 0ebd78dc-f598-4308-9684-e5c5adca2810"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821144695","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821144694"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 0ebd78dc-f598-4308-9684-e5c5adca2810"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821145687","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821145687"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 0ebd78dc-f598-4308-9684-e5c5adca2810"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821145950","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821145949"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 0ebd78dc-f598-4308-9684-e5c5adca2810"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821146902","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821146901"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 0ebd78dc-f598-4308-9684-e5c5adca2810"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821149838","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821149838"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 0ebd78dc-f598-4308-9684-e5c5adca2810"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821150886","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821150885"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 0ebd78dc-f598-4308-9684-e5c5adca2810"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821151373","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821151373"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 0ebd78dc-f598-4308-9684-e5c5adca2810"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821155971","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821155969"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 0ebd78dc-f598-4308-9684-e5c5adca2810"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821156128","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821156128"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 0ebd78dc-f598-4308-9684-e5c5adca2810"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821184260","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821184260"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALIKUWA"," userResponse":" PALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821184502","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821184502"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821184961","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821184961"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821185402","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821185402"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821185725","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821185725"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TU"," userResponse":" TU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821186531","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821186531"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821187138","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821187138"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" KIJIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821187397","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821187397"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821188192","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821188192"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EBEI"," userResponse":" EBEI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821195614","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821195613"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821204405","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821204405"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821207773","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821207773"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821210101","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821210101"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821215245","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821215245"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821217303","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821217302"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821219356","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821219356"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821226861","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821226861"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821229151","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821229150"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821231358","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821231358"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EBEI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821233437","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821233437"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa kubwa na ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821234410","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821234410"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa kubwa na ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821234843","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821234843"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa kubwa na ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821235026","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821235026"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa kubwa na ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821235636","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821235635"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa kubwa na ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BULUU"," userResponse":" BULUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821239749","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821239749"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa kubwa na ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821241684","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821241684"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa kubwa na ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821243280","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821243280"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa kubwa na ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821245299","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821245299"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa kubwa na ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821247673","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821247673"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa kubwa na ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821250546","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821250545"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa kubwa na ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BULUU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821251313","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821251313"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilitoa kelele sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ILITOA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821252900","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821252899"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilitoa kelele sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILITOA"," userResponse":" ILITOA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821253533","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821253533"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilitoa kelele sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KELELE"," userResponse":" KELELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821253646","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821253646"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilitoa kelele sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821257708","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821257708"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilitoa kelele sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ILITOA"," userResponse":" TU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821259137","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821259136"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilitoa kelele sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ILITOA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821260812","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821260811"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilitoa kelele sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILITOA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821262303","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821262303"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilitoa kelele sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KELELE"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821264427","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821264426"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilitoa kelele sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KELELE"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821266299","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821266298"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilitoa kelele sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KELELE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821267281","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821267281"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilitoa kelele sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821268271","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821268271"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilitoa kelele sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821270524","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821270523"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821271198","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821271197"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821272062","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821272061"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821272293","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821272293"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821273059","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821273058"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EBEI"," userResponse":" EBEI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821273926","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821273926"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821275025","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821275024"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KESHO"," userResponse":" KESHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821276062","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821276062"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUTAKWENDA"," userResponse":" TUTAKWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821276993","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821276992"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJINI"," userResponse":" MJINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821278077","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821278077"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNUNUA"," userResponse":" KUNUNUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821278517","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821278515"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SARE"," userResponse":" SARE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821279130","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821279130"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKO"," userResponse":" YAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821279314","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821279313"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821279897","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821279897"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULE"," userResponse":" SHULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821283092","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821283092"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821285266","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821285266"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821287145","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821287145"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821288727","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821288727"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821290603","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821290603"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821290725","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821290725"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" EBEI"," userResponse":" SHULE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821293545","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821293545"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" EBEI"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821295409","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821295409"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EBEI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821295902","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821295902"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821297196","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821297195"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821298950","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821298949"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821300818","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821300818"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KESHO"," userResponse":" START_TUTAKWENDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821301984","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821301983"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KESHO"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821303439","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821303439"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KESHO"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821305951","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821305950"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" TUTAKWENDA"," userResponse":" MJINI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821308686","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821308686"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUTAKWENDA"," userResponse":" TUTAKWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821309287","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821309287"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJINI"," userResponse":" MJINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821309667","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821309666"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNUNUA"," userResponse":" KUNUNUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821312896","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821312895"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SARE"," userResponse":" SARE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821317000","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821317000"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" YAKO"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821321447","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821321447"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKO"," userResponse":" YAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821323047","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821323047"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821325194","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821325193"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821327776","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821327776"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alifurahi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EBEI"," userResponse":" EBEI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821328944","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821328943"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alifurahi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFURAHI"," userResponse":" ALIFURAHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821329669","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821329669"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alifurahi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821331359","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821331359"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alifurahi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EBEI"," userResponse":" EBEI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821331849","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821331849"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alifurahi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFURAHI"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821340319","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821340319"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alifurahi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFURAHI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821343655","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821343655"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alifurahi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821346258","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821346257"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angesafiria katika ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGESAFIRIA"," userResponse":" ANGESAFIRIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821346887","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821346886"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angesafiria katika ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821347310","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821347310"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angesafiria katika ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILE"," userResponse":" ILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821347814","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821347814"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angesafiria katika ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821348301","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821348300"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angesafiria katika ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821348531","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821348526"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angesafiria katika ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821349232","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821349232"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angesafiria katika ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BULUU"," userResponse":" BULUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821353964","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821353964"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angesafiria katika ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGESAFIRIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821356757","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821356756"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angesafiria katika ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821361572","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821361572"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angesafiria katika ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821363540","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821363540"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angesafiria katika ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821369409","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821369409"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angesafiria katika ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821370950","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821370950"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angesafiria katika ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821372097","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821372097"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angesafiria katika ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BULUU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821374209","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821374209"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuweza kulala usiku huo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUWEZA"," userResponse":" HAKUWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821374783","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821374783"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuweza kulala usiku huo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULALA"," userResponse":" KULALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821375306","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821375306"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuweza kulala usiku huo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USIKU"," userResponse":" USIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821375764","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821375763"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuweza kulala usiku huo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUO"," userResponse":" HUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821380159","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821380159"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuweza kulala usiku huo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUWEZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821385372","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821385372"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuweza kulala usiku huo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULALA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821388050","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821388050"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuweza kulala usiku huo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" USIKU"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821389372","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821389372"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuweza kulala usiku huo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" USIKU"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821391048","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821391047"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuweza kulala usiku huo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USIKU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821393345","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821393344"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuweza kulala usiku huo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HUO"," userResponse":" ILE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821395208","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821395208"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuweza kulala usiku huo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821397525","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821397525"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alikuwa tayari amevaa wakati mama yake alikwenda kumuamsha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EBEI"," userResponse":" EBEI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821398281","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821398281"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alikuwa tayari amevaa wakati mama yake alikwenda kumuamsha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821399224","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821399223"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alikuwa tayari amevaa wakati mama yake alikwenda kumuamsha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAYARI"," userResponse":" TAYARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821400579","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821400579"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alikuwa tayari amevaa wakati mama yake alikwenda kumuamsha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEVAA"," userResponse":" AMEVAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821401242","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821401242"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alikuwa tayari amevaa wakati mama yake alikwenda kumuamsha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821401618","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821401617"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alikuwa tayari amevaa wakati mama yake alikwenda kumuamsha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821402151","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821402151"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alikuwa tayari amevaa wakati mama yake alikwenda kumuamsha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821403240","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821403238"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alikuwa tayari amevaa wakati mama yake alikwenda kumuamsha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKWENDA"," userResponse":" ALIKWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821404347","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821404347"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alikuwa tayari amevaa wakati mama yake alikwenda kumuamsha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMUAMSHA"," userResponse":" KUMUAMSHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821406937","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821406936"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alikuwa tayari amevaa wakati mama yake alikwenda kumuamsha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" EBEI"," userResponse":" AMEVAA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821407858","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821407858"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alikuwa tayari amevaa wakati mama yake alikwenda kumuamsha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EBEI"," userResponse":" EBEI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821409752","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821409752"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alikuwa tayari amevaa wakati mama yake alikwenda kumuamsha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821412249","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821412249"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alikuwa tayari amevaa wakati mama yake alikwenda kumuamsha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" TAYARI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821421817","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821421817"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alikuwa tayari amevaa wakati mama yake alikwenda kumuamsha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAYARI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821427303","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821427303"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alikuwa tayari amevaa wakati mama yake alikwenda kumuamsha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEVAA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821430237","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821430237"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alikuwa tayari amevaa wakati mama yake alikwenda kumuamsha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821432388","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821432388"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alikuwa tayari amevaa wakati mama yake alikwenda kumuamsha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821437093","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821437093"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alikuwa tayari amevaa wakati mama yake alikwenda kumuamsha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821441682","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821441682"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alikuwa tayari amevaa wakati mama yake alikwenda kumuamsha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKWENDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821526377","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821526376"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alikuwa tayari amevaa wakati mama yake alikwenda kumuamsha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUMUAMSHA"," userResponse":" START_ALIKWENDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821527657","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821527657"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alikuwa tayari amevaa wakati mama yake alikwenda kumuamsha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMUAMSHA"," userResponse":" KUMUAMSHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821530087","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821530087"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei na mama yake walitembea kwenda katika kituo cha basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EBEI"," userResponse":" EBEI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821530308","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821530307"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei na mama yake walitembea kwenda katika kituo cha basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821530705","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821530704"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei na mama yake walitembea kwenda katika kituo cha basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821531219","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821531218"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei na mama yake walitembea kwenda katika kituo cha basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821532412","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821532412"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei na mama yake walitembea kwenda katika kituo cha basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALITEMBEA"," userResponse":" WALITEMBEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821533276","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821533276"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei na mama yake walitembea kwenda katika kituo cha basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821534310","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821534309"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei na mama yake walitembea kwenda katika kituo cha basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821534943","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821534943"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei na mama yake walitembea kwenda katika kituo cha basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITUO"," userResponse":" KITUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821535197","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821535197"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei na mama yake walitembea kwenda katika kituo cha basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821535771","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821535771"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei na mama yake walitembea kwenda katika kituo cha basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821538324","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821538324"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei na mama yake walitembea kwenda katika kituo cha basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" EBEI"," userResponse":" KITUO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821545540","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821545539"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei na mama yake walitembea kwenda katika kituo cha basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EBEI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821547864","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821547864"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei na mama yake walitembea kwenda katika kituo cha basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821553385","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821553385"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei na mama yake walitembea kwenda katika kituo cha basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821559209","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821559209"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei na mama yake walitembea kwenda katika kituo cha basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821566292","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821566292"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei na mama yake walitembea kwenda katika kituo cha basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALITEMBEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821569107","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821569107"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei na mama yake walitembea kwenda katika kituo cha basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821571719","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821571719"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei na mama yake walitembea kwenda katika kituo cha basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821573773","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821573772"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei na mama yake walitembea kwenda katika kituo cha basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITUO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821575263","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821575263"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei na mama yake walitembea kwenda katika kituo cha basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821589446","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821589446"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei na mama yake walitembea kwenda katika kituo cha basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821596722","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821596722"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei na mama yake walitembea kwenda katika kituo cha basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821598357","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821598356"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei na mama yake walitembea kwenda katika kituo cha basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821600867","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821600867"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walisubiri ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALISUBIRI"," userResponse":" WALISUBIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821601226","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821601225"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walisubiri ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILE"," userResponse":" ILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821601697","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821601697"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walisubiri ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821602278","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821602278"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walisubiri ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821602483","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821602483"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walisubiri ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821603081","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821603080"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walisubiri ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BULUU"," userResponse":" BULUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821609349","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821609348"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walisubiri ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WALISUBIRI"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821610407","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821610407"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walisubiri ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WALISUBIRI"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821612313","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821612313"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walisubiri ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALISUBIRI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821613080","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821613080"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walisubiri ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ILE"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821618927","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821618927"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walisubiri ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ILE"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821620406","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821620406"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walisubiri ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821621089","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821621089"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walisubiri ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821623781","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821623781"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walisubiri ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821626561","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821626560"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walisubiri ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821635599","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821635599"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walisubiri ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821637209","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821637209"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walisubiri ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821639036","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821639036"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walisubiri ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" BULUU"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821640902","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821640902"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walisubiri ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" BULUU"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821640943","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821640942"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walisubiri ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BULUU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821642616","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821642616"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini basi haikufika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821643076","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821643075"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini basi haikufika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821644288","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821644288"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini basi haikufika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAIKUFIKA"," userResponse":" HAIKUFIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821652364","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821652364"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini basi haikufika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821673694","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821673693"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini basi haikufika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821677674","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821677674"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini basi haikufika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821679326","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821679326"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini basi haikufika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821679625","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821679625"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini basi haikufika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HAIKUFIKA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821681923","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821681923"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini basi haikufika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" HAIKUFIKA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821683693","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821683692"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini basi haikufika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAIKUFIKA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821685356","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821685355"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walifika pale kwenye kituo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821685977","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821685977"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walifika pale kwenye kituo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821686652","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821686652"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walifika pale kwenye kituo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821687061","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821687061"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walifika pale kwenye kituo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIFIKA"," userResponse":" WENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821687327","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821687327"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walifika pale kwenye kituo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALE"," userResponse":" WALIFIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821687804","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821687803"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walifika pale kwenye kituo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" PALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821687871","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821687871"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walifika pale kwenye kituo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITUO"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821935252","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821935252"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Watu wengine walifika pale kwenye kituo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821935343","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821935343"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" acb3bfe4-225b-4161-8d72-5a9f1238ea82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walifika pale kwenye kituo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITUO"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821948728","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821948727"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALIKUWA"," userResponse":" PALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821948973","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821948972"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821949426","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821949425"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821949878","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821949878"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821950199","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821950199"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TU"," userResponse":" TU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821951002","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821951002"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821951605","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821951605"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" KIJIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821951868","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821951867"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821952658","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821952658"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EBEI"," userResponse":" EBEI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821962795","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821962795"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" PALIKUWA"," userResponse":" EBEI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821968011","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821968011"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALIKUWA"," userResponse":" PALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821968340","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821968339"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821969446","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821969446"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821969449","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821969449"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821970235","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821970234"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TU"," userResponse":" TU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821982734","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821982733"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821986648","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821986648"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821990033","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821990032"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821990801","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821990801"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821991528","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821991527"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" EBEI"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821992568","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821992568"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" EBEI"," userResponse":" KIJIJI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821994364","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821994363"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EBEI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821996465","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821996464"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa kubwa na ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821997453","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821997452"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa kubwa na ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821997905","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821997904"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa kubwa na ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821998088","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821998088"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa kubwa na ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549821998690","data":{"timestamp":" 1549821998689"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa kubwa na ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BULUU"," userResponse":" BULUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822001087","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822001086"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa kubwa na ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822002983","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822002982"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa kubwa na ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822004755","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822004753"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa kubwa na ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822006248","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822006248"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa kubwa na ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822008770","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822008770"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa kubwa na ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822008941","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822008941"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa kubwa na ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822011049","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822011049"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa kubwa na ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822013286","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822013286"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa kubwa na ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822013489","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822013489"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa kubwa na ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BULUU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822015816","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822015816"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilitoa kelele sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILITOA"," userResponse":" ILITOA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822016452","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822016451"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilitoa kelele sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KELELE"," userResponse":" KELELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822017214","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822017213"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilitoa kelele sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822019572","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822019571"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilitoa kelele sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ILITOA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822021661","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822021661"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilitoa kelele sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ILITOA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822023272","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822023271"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilitoa kelele sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILITOA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822025458","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822025457"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilitoa kelele sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KELELE"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822034161","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822034160"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilitoa kelele sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KELELE"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822036030","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822036030"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilitoa kelele sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KELELE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822040443","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822040442"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilitoa kelele sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822042411","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822042411"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilitoa kelele sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822044658","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822044657"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822045334","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822045334"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822046198","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822046198"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822046428","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822046428"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822047194","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822047194"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EBEI"," userResponse":" EBEI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822048077","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822048071"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822049170","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822049170"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KESHO"," userResponse":" KESHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822050199","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822050198"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUTAKWENDA"," userResponse":" TUTAKWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822051121","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822051120"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJINI"," userResponse":" MJINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822052196","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822052195"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNUNUA"," userResponse":" KUNUNUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822052619","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822052618"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SARE"," userResponse":" SARE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822053235","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822053235"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKO"," userResponse":" YAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822053418","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822053418"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822054004","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822054003"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULE"," userResponse":" SHULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822057183","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822057183"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822060402","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822060402"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822061273","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822061272"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822062313","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822062313"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822063040","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822063040"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" KUNUNUA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822064552","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822064552"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822064696","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822064696"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" EBEI"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822066020","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822066020"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EBEI"," userResponse":" EBEI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822067863","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822067863"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" SHULE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822069590","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822069590"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" TUTAKWENDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822071360","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822071359"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822072141","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822072141"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KESHO"," userResponse":" MJINI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822072963","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822072963"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KESHO"," userResponse":" KESHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822074599","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822074598"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" TUTAKWENDA"," userResponse":" START_TUTAKWENDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822078141","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822078141"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" TUTAKWENDA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822079978","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822079978"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUTAKWENDA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822080147","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822080147"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MJINI"," userResponse":" KESHO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822081840","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822081840"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MJINI"," userResponse":" YAKO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822083176","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822083175"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJINI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822083547","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822083547"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUNUNUA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822086459","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822086458"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNUNUA"," userResponse":" KUNUNUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822088944","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822088944"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SARE"," userResponse":" KUNUNUA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822090800","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822090800"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SARE"," userResponse":" SARE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822091715","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822091715"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" YAKO"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822094521","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822094520"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKO"," userResponse":" YAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822094866","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822094866"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822096473","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822096473"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULE"," userResponse":" SHULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822099079","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822099079"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alifurahi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EBEI"," userResponse":" EBEI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822100244","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822100243"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alifurahi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFURAHI"," userResponse":" ALIFURAHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822100971","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822100970"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alifurahi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822102802","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822102802"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alifurahi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EBEI"," userResponse":" EBEI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822104291","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822104290"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alifurahi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFURAHI"," userResponse":" ALIFURAHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822104397","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822104397"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alifurahi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822107014","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822107013"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angesafiria katika ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGESAFIRIA"," userResponse":" ANGESAFIRIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822107635","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822107635"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angesafiria katika ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822108068","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822108068"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angesafiria katika ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILE"," userResponse":" ILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822108581","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822108581"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angesafiria katika ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822109080","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822109080"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angesafiria katika ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822109296","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822109296"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angesafiria katika ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822110001","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822110001"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angesafiria katika ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BULUU"," userResponse":" BULUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822112341","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822112341"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angesafiria katika ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ANGESAFIRIA"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822115049","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822115049"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angesafiria katika ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGESAFIRIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822117782","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822117781"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Angesafiria katika ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822117938","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822117937"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angesafiria katika ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGESAFIRIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..10.off1.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822164504","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822164504"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Angesafiria katika ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.4.lc.rand.stat.show.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822184522","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822184521"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 089b7fa2-2b19-445d-9ff5-82bdb6466693"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Angesafiria katika ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822193736","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822193735"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 40dc84da-7ff3-4dda-9db5-20e7ffe76218"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822193959","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822193959"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 40dc84da-7ff3-4dda-9db5-20e7ffe76218"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822194324","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822194324"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 40dc84da-7ff3-4dda-9db5-20e7ffe76218"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822194402","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822194401"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 40dc84da-7ff3-4dda-9db5-20e7ffe76218"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822205710","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822205709"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_204510"," gameId":" 40dc84da-7ff3-4dda-9db5-20e7ffe76218"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}